sualize.us 2015-12-29

# Privacy Policy on VisualizeUs

The privacy of our visitors and users to VisualizeUs is very important to us.

At VisualizeUs, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit VisualizeUs, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

### Information Collection and Use

We may collect personal information, including email addresses, when individuals register to use the VisualizeUs site and services, post a favorite picture on VisualizeUs or submit questions, comments or bug reports. We may also, at times, collect our users' IP addresses and information regarding our users' use of the site and services. We may use such IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement within our site and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Use. We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times and browser type. Unless required by law, we will not share our users' personal information, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and usage information, except with their consent or in aggregate or anonymous form, with third parties.

You will receive notifications on your e-mail in a number of cases, such as when a VisualizeUs member adds you as a friend. Our service give you the opportunity to opt-out to stop receiving any of these communications from us. If you contact us by email through the site, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you.

### Links to Third Party Web Sites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from VisualizeUs nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful or interesting to the users of the site, or provided by our users to give you more information about themselves. Please remember that when you use a link to go from VisualizeUs to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. By your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link on VisualizeUs, is subject to that website's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

### Our Policy Towards Children

The site is not directed to persons under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files.

### Log Files

As with most other sites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as your account.

We also use third party advertisements on VisualizeUs to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other sites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.
